Excuse me.
Would it be okay if I took
that basket, straw and some bamboo?
Sure, you're welcome to it,
but that basket's full of holes.
Yes. I'll pay you for it.
No, that's all right.
I mean, it's a basket with holes.
Yes, I will pay you!
No, it's all right. You can have
the bamboo and straw for free, too.
But I'm still paying you!
I said it's okay!
You're one stubborn kid!
Please accept this,
although it's just small change!
Thank you very much!
Ouch!
Nezuko?
Huh? Nezuko?
She's gone!
There she is.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
EPISODE 2:
TRAINER SAKONJI UROKODAKI
Nezuko...
She dug a hole?
My kid sister's turned into a mole.
And she's frowning!
She must really want
to avoid the sunlight.
Wait there for a second!
Nezuko?
Think you can fit inside this?
I want to keep moving
during the day, too.
I'll carry you, okay?
Can you fit?
In here?
Basket.
She kinda protrudes, huh?
I can't believe she grew up.
Seems like yesterday that she was tiny.
Nezuko?
Remember how you became big
like an adult earlier?
Do you think you can do
the opposite? Get smaller?
Smaller, Nezuko!
Get smaller!
Good job!
That's a good girl, Nezuko!
I'm impressed!
Mt. Sagiri?
If you want to go to Mt. Sagiri,
you'll have to cross over that mountain, but...
The sun's about to set. Are you really
heading there with all that luggage?
It's dangerous, you know.
I'll be careful.
Thank you very much.
People have gone missing lately!
Try not to lose your way!
There's a temple over there.
There's light leaking through,
so someone must be there.
Let's check it out.
I smell blood!
This mountain path is pretty rough!
Someone must've gotten hurt!
Are you all right?
What the hell?
This is my turf.
If you break into my territory,
I'll make you pay!
It's a man-eating demon!
There's something off about you.
Are you both humans?
A hatchet, huh? Not bad.
But a scratch like this...
should heal in no time.
See that? The bleeding's stopped already.
He's so fast!
And he's unbelievably strong!
You won't get me twice!
All right.
I'm gonna snap your neck!
Sh-She killed him!
Oh, but wait! He's a demon, so...
N-Nezuko...
I don't believe this!
Did he just move without his head?!
You bastards!
One of you is a demon after all?
You gave off such a weird vibe!
What's a human and a demon
doing teaming up?
He's actually talking!
Stop it!
Nezuko!
What's the deal with this guy?
Growing arms from his head!
I gotta save Nezuko!
Out of my way!
Hard as a rock!
That head of his...
Like a rock!
Okay!
I wrapped my hair around his hatchet
to grab it, but it got tangled up! Dammit!
Nezuko! Where are you?
Nezuko!
Stop it!
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
I wonder if there are tons
of demons out there.
This isn't the scent
that was lingering in my house.
That was a different demon...
But...
I gotta finish him off...
or he'll attack more people!
So...
I gotta do it!
Do it!
You can't finish him off with that.
A goblin mask!
I didn't hear his footsteps!
H-How can I finish him off?
Don't ask me!
Can't you use your own head
to figure that out?
If stabbing's no good,
I'll have to crush his head!
To crush his skull
and smash it completely,
I guess I'm going to have to pound him
with this rock many times.
I bet he's going to suffer.
Isn't there anything I can use
to kill him with one blow?
This kid isn't going to cut it.
He's too kind and can't make decisions.
He's facing a demon,
yet the scent of kindness remains.
He has empathy for even a demon.
Giyu...
He's never going to make it.
I blacked out.
Is my body dead, then?
I feel sick!
You bastard, I'll kill you!
I swear I'll devour you!
Get over here! Dammit!
I can't go to you, so you come to me!
I faltered too long.
Now the sun's coming up!
Hey, are you listening, brat?
Hey, come here, you!
Are you listening, you brat?
He's gone with that much sunlight?!
No wonder Nezuko shrinks from it!
Nezuko?
Nezuko...
O-Oh, that's right.
Where's that man?
He buried the people who got killed.
Um...
I'm Sakonji Urokodaki.
I'm assuming you're the one
Giyu Tomioka sent my way.
Yes! My name is Tanjiro Kamado!
My sister's name is Nezuko, and...
Tanjiro...
What will you do
when your sister devours a human?
Too slow!
You're just too slow
at making decisions!
You failed to finish off that demon
before daybreak!
Do you know why you couldn't answer
my question right away?
It's because your resolve is too weak!
There are two things to do
if your sister devours a human.
Kill your sister!
And slit your own belly and die!
That's what it means to travel
with your sister who became a demon!
But that must never happen no matter what.
And you'd best not forget.
Your sister, taking the life
of an innocent person...
That's the one thing
that must never happen. Ever!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes!
All right, now I'm going to test you
to see if you're fit to become
a member of the Demon Slayer Corps.
Carry your sister on your back
and follow me!
He's so fast!
Just how old is he anyway?
And, like earlier,
I'm not hearing any footsteps at all!
Nezuko, I know it must be jarring,
but please be patient!
Well, being patient
is all that you've ever known.
Nezuko...
All your life...
You're fixing your kimono again?
I guess we'll have to buy you a new one.
No, no, it's all right!
This kimono's my favorite!
I'd rather the younger kids
got more food to fill them up!
I swear I'll turn you back into a human!
I swear I'll buy you
a beautiful kimono someday!
Everything that I couldn't do
for the others...
I'll do it all for you!
N-Now, have I...
passed the test?
The test starts now.
We're going to climb a mountain.
I'll make sure to take care
of your sister for you.
I'm counting on you, sir.
I'm so exhausted.
My legs are starting to buckle!
I'm starting to feel dizzy, too.
Now, from here, go back down to the house
at the foot of the mountain.
This time, I'm not going to wait
until daybreak!
Is that all?
I see.
He thinks I might get lost
in this thick fog.
I just have to get back
by daybreak, right?
That's easy!
I've got a great sense of smell!
I've already memorized
Mr. Urokodaki's scent!
Rocks?!
A pitfall?
I get it now.
So, there are traps all around!
That's the deal, huh?
Uh-oh!
Crap, crap, crap!
If I keep walking into traps like this,
I won't make it down the mountain
by morning!
And besides, this mountain...
This mountain is...
The air's thin here!
It's way thinner here than on the mountain
where I used to live!
That's why I'm gasping for air
like this and feel so dizzy!
Will I make it back?
I might pass out!
No!
I gotta make it back!
Get your breathing under control...
and sniff out each of those traps!
Right! I've got it! I've got it!
Traps set by human hands
have a slightly different smell after all!
But that doesn't mean...
I'm suddenly athletic enough
to dodge every one of them!
I'm gonna make it back
no matter what!
Nezuko!
I... have... returned.
Forgive my abruptness,
Mr. Sakonji Urokodaki.
I'm sending a boy your way who wants
to become a Demon Slayer swordsman.
He was brazen enough
to attack me unarmed.
His family was slaughtered by a demon,
and the surviving younger sister
has become one,
but I have determined
that she will not attack humans.
I can sense something different
about these two.
Like yourself, the boy seems
to have a keen sense of smell.
Perhaps he'll find a way to break through
and become your heir apparent.
I am asking you to train him.
I realize that this is
a self-serving request,
but please forgive me.
I hope that you will take good care
of yourself in your endeavors.
Yours truly...
Giyu Tomioka.
I accept you as my student,
Tanjiro Kamado.
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
The demon in the temple surprised us
quite a bit, right?
I never expected
to see arms grow from his head.
Now that I'm accepted
by Mr. Urokodaki, I'll do my best!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
Mr. Urokodaki with the goblin mask...
Believe it or not, his age is—
Tanjiro!
Yes?
Which do you want for dinner?
Nikujaga or oden?
Huh? Well...
Too slow to decide!
I want oden!
Next, Episode 3, "Sabito and Makomo"!
TO BE CONTINUED
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6y8zk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles