Nezuko: Blood Demon art.
Exploding blood!
( Rui gasps )
¶
Tanjiro: The bond
between Nezuko and I
cannot be severed,
not by anyone!
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
¶
Tanjiro: Nezuko.
Nezuko!
( Groans )
I won. I did it!
- ( Bells jingle )
- My Father saved me.
Our family's kagura,
which has been passed down
for generations,
somehow manifested itself
into a technique
and helped me defeat that Demon.
( Groans )
Huh?
My vision's blurry.
Is it because I took
too many breaths too fast?
- ( Gasping )
- ( Tone buzzing )
This ringing in my ears
is agonizing.
My whole body
is throbbing with pain.
( Groans ) I need to catch
my second wind...
And press on.
The fight's not over, not yet.
I still need to go save Inosuke
as soon as I can.
¶
( gasps )
The scent of blood
just got stronger,
and it didn't give off
the smell of ash like usual.
Don't tell me.
¶
- could he have survived that?
- ( Threads creak )
Rui: You thought
you'd defeated me?
How sad for you.
Did your delusion bring you
a brief moment of joy?
I cut my head off myself
using my own threads...
Before you were able
to do the job yourself.
- ( Tanjiro groans )
- Rui: Enough struggling.
I'll kill both you
and your sister.
I haven't been this incensed
in a long time.
Tanjiro: Get up!
Get on your feet.
You need to control
your breathing.
Hurry! There's no time!
Rui: I wonder why you weren't
burned to cinders earlier
in that explosion.
Me and my threads
were the only things
that were set ablaze.
I don't know if it relates
to your sister's power,
but it has enraged me
all the same.
Now I'm going to carve you up
without regret.
Tanjiro: If I use
the correct breathing technique,
it doesn't matter
how exhausted I am.
Rui: Blood Demon art.
Murderous eye basket.
( Threads whipping )
Tanjiro: Don't let your
breathing be disrupted, Tanjiro.
Calm down. Just stay calm.
¶
I can't raise my arm.
( Groans )
¶
somebody's here.
Is it Zenitsu?
Tomioka: You did a good job
holding out until I got here.
Leave the rest to me.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Rui: You're like
an endless torrent
of insignificant insects,
constantly getting in my way.
Blood Demon art.
¶
cutting thread rotation!
Tomioka: Total concentration.
Water breathing. 11th form...
- Dead calm.
- ( Drop echoes )
Tanjiro: The 11th form?
Rui: It doesn't matter
what technique you use on me!
( Threads ripping )
What?
What's going on?
What did he do?
The instant they touched him,
the threads scattered.
Not even one of them
reached him.
The strongest threads of all
were destroyed?
That cannot be!
I'll try it again!
( Sister panting )
I messed up. I really messed up.
This whole time we were
pretending to be a family,
I was the only one
who had a perfect track record,
until now!
( Panting )
( Yelps )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Gasps )
Demon Slayer:
We've finally cornered her.
Demon Slayer 2: Hey, look.
Demon Slayer 1: Huh?
¶
Demon Slayer 2: A Demon?
Demon Slayer 1:
It's just a runt,
but even if it looks like a kid,
it's still a threat.
If we let it go,
it'll devour humans.
Rui: You there...
Tell me, do you
want me to save you?
Sister: What?
Rui: I will do so
if you'll do whatever I ask.
( Sister gasps ) Yes, I accept!
I'll do whatever you want!
Just save me!
Rui: So then,
you'll become part of my family?
Sister: Yes! Just help me!
Demon Slayer 1:
What are they talking about?
All right, it's over for you!
( Women vocalizing )
- ( Rustling )
- ( Wood clattering )
( Sister gasps )
Rui: Welcome home.
Starting today, you will
also be part of my family.
Demon: Drink this.
The strength
that exists in our family
is all thanks to Rui.
And since all of US
were quite weak,
Rui shared his power with US.
He is a favorite
of a certain someone,
and because of that,
he has permission to do this.
( Sister sighs )
( Gasps )
( Gagging )
Rui: Do you feel it?
There's no need to fear
those Demon slayers any longer.
Now, then...
Time for the finishing touches.
( Sister screams )
( Panting )
Rui: Good. You can look now.
Congratulations.
You're truly part of the family.
¶
Demon: We're only playing house.
Sister: What?
Demon: There's
no blood relation.
We're just a band of strangers.
Mother: I'm so sorry!
I'll do better, Rui!
I'll work harder to keep it
from happening! I promise!
I didn't mean
to revert to this form.
It just happens
by accident sometimes.
- ( Thread creaks )
- ( Gasps )
( Gagging )
Rui: I don't want
your excuses, Mother.
( Mother coughs )
Rui: You will play
your assigned role.
Mother: I understand, Rui.
Demon: We were so scared
of the Demon slayers
and sought companionship.
But this charade,
I don't think that was
what any of US had in mind
when we agreed to this.
But at the end of the day,
those who disappoint him
are punished.
They get carved up,
have their intellect taken,
or are forced
to burn in the sunlight.
I can't take it any longer.
Sister: I'll pretend
I never heard that. Instead--
Demon: I can tell
that you're not like the others.
( Sister gasps )
Demon: You're
much more enlightened.
Let's run away together.
¶
I wouldn't say this
to anyone but you.
You're the one person I truly
think of as my younger sister.
( Both panting )
Demon: Tomorrow, Rui will be
summoned by that man
and descend the mountain.
That will be
our chance to escape.
( Gasps )
¶
( Groaning )
Rui: How disappointing.
¶
( Birds chirping )
( Sizzling )
Sister: They were all fools,
but I'm not like them!
And yet, I still messed up!
Rui. Rui!
Mother's been killed
and our elder brother, too!
What now? The Demon slayers
aren't far behind US.
Rui...
Sh-shouldn't we
make a run for it?
No.
( Screams )
- ( Sobbing )
- Rui: I've told you before.
I really hate it when your face
changes back like that.
( Wood clatters )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Rui: What are you looking at?
This isn't a play, you know.
Sister: I only
got my face slashed.
I got off easy.
( Murata gasps ) A Demon!
What the...
( Grunts )
Sister: It's no use.
That won't work.
My ball of yarn may feel soft,
but it's also quite durable.
- ( Oozing )
- ( Murata screams )
Sister: First, the solvent
will melt your clothes
down to nothing,
and then it'll be your turn.
After you're reduced to a pulp,
I will feed on your remains.
Shinobu: Wow! That's incredible!
Do you release those threads
from the palms of your hands?
( Sister gasps )
Shinobu: Good evening.
The moon's quite lovely tonight,
isn't it?
( Sister gasps )
¶
( Sister groaning )
Shinobu: I can see
you have no intention
of being my friend, now, do you?
Sister: No. Wait!
Let me explain!
Someone's--someone's
forcing me to do all this!
If I don't,
I'll be torn to pieces.
Shinobu: My,
is that really true?
That does sound tragic.
I'll save you!
So let's be friends!
Sister: You--you're
going to save me?
Shinobu: Of course!
But in order for US
to be friends,
I must ask you
a few questions first.
( Sister gasps )
Shinobu: Tell me,
my sweet child,
how many have you
been responsible for killing?
Sister: Five humans.
( Gasps ) But I was ordered to.
I didn't have a choice.
Shinobu: Now, now.
There's no need to lie about it.
I know the truth.
That spell you cast to turn
one of our men into a cocoon
was most impressive.
You've eaten at least 80 humans.
Sister: I don't know
what you're saying.
I've only killed those five.
Shinobu: I happened
to come to this place
from the west, you know.
I saw things differently.
It was there that I witnessed
hordes of cocoons...
Hanging from the trees.
The human captives inside had
been liquefied, all massacred.
In that spot alone,
I counted at least 14 cocoons,
14 humans, all dead and gone.
Oh, don't mistake me
for being angry.
I'm just checking
if the death toll
is an accurate one.
Sister: What good does it do
for you to confirm that?
Shinobu: So I can see
you receive the proper penalty
and be reborn.
- Sister: Penalty?
- Shinobu: Yes!
That way, you and I
can become friends.
If you go unpunished after
having taken all those lives,
your victims
will never receive justice.
( Sister gasps )
Shinobu: I could
gouge out your eyeballs
or perhaps slash your stomach
and rip out your organs.
For every life you've taken,
I'll exact the same amount
of pain on you,
and after you've
suffered through
all of the agony required,
your sins will be forgiven.
- Let's both give it our all.
- ( Sister shuddering )
Shinobu: Don't worry, my dear!
You are a Demon after all,
so none of this will kill you
or leave any lingering effects.
Sister: Who do you think
you're kidding?!
Die, you damn witch!
¶
Shinobu: I can see that we'll
never be friends after all.
Aw, what a pity.
( Sister gasps )
Eh? ( Gasps )
( Women singing in Japanese )
( Gasping )
Shinobu: Insect breathing.
Butterfly dance...
And caprice.
( Sister gasps )
My head, it hasn't been cut off.
That's the sword she's using?
I see. She's too tiny
and has no arm strength,
so she can't behead me.
Her life is mine.
- ( Heart beating )
- ( Gasping )
( Gagging )
¶
Shinobu: Just because
you haven't been beheaded,
don't think
that you're safe from harm.
There are those like me, who use
poison with their swordsmanship.
Demon Slayer Corps,
insect Hashira, Shinobu Kocho.
I may be the only one
among the Hashira
who is unable
to decapitate demons,
but creating a poison
that's lethal to them,
that's quite impressive,
don't you think?
Oh! Pardon me!
I guess you can't hear me
if you're dead.
Silly me!
( Sword slices )
( Murata groaning )
( Coughing )
Shinobu: Are you all right, sir?
Murata: Just barely.
What happened to the Demon?
Shouldn't you finish it off
or something?
Shinobu: I infected her
with Wisteria poison.
She's already dead.
We can leave her to rot.
If you were curious,
I'm an expert in pharmaceutics.
Your clothes were dissolved,
but your body
is more or less unscathed!
- I'm so glad!
- ( Murata whimpering )
Shinobu: Now, then,
to find the whereabouts
of the Demon she mentioned
who was forcing her
to do its bidding.
Though I wonder if Tomioka
has already finished the job.
Tanjiro: Nezuko, I'm coming.
Rui: I'll kill them.
I'll kill them.
I'll kill
that brother and sister,
no matter the cost!
Mother: What it
that is you want, Rui?
What do you mean by "family"?
Rui: I'm not sure.
I have no memories
of when I was human, you see.
Mother: Is that why you made US
pretend to be your family?
Rui: I thought that,
if I could feel a family bond,
my memories would come back.
¶
the bond of a real family.
That's right.
I remember.
Tanjiro: Nezuko.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-