Come on out, demon!
Stop it!
Look, it's the human blood
you love so much!
KILL
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
EPISODE 23:
HASHIRA MEETING
What's the matter, demon? Come on!
You know you want it.
Iguro, you're digging into him too hard.
Ease up a bit please.
I'm only holding him down
because he's trying to move.
Kamado,
if you use any breathing techniques
while your lungs are being squeezed,
your veins will burst.
His veins will burst!
I like it! Sounds flamboyant!
Come on! Start bursting!
Poor soul...
Such a weak, pathetic child.
Namu Amida Butsu.
Kamado?
DESTROY
Nezuko!
She's my sister!
She's my younger sister!
Nezuko is different!
Though I don't know how it happened!
All humans are your family.
Protect humans.
Humans are to be protected and saved.
Never hurt them.
I will never hurt them.
What just happened?
The demon girl turned her back in disgust.
Although she'd been stabbed
three times by Shinazugawa,
and despite his flaunting
of his bloody arm in her face,
she restrained herself and did not bite.
So now, it's been proven
that Nezuko won't attack humans, right?
What do you think you're doing, Tomioka?
Tanjiro...
I'm sure that even after this,
there are some who can't accept Nezuko.
You must prove it to them starting now.
That you and Nezuko can fight
as Demon Slayers.
That you can be useful.
What is this feeling?
It's like I'm floating.
His voice...
Is it because of this man's voice
that I'm feeling light in the head?
Go out and defeat a Twelve Kizuki.
Do that, and you'll be accepted by all.
And it will give more weight to your words.
I...
Nezuko and I will defeat Muzan Kibutsuji!
Nezuko and I will do it for sure!
Strike with the sword
that will stop the chain of grief!
As you're ill-equipped to do so
right now, Tanjiro,
let's start by defeating
a Twelve Kizuki, all right?
Yes, sir.
You mustn't laugh!
You mustn't, you mustn't, you mustn't!
It goes without saying
that the Hashiras of the Demon Slayer Corps
have phenomenal skills.
After training themselves to death,
they have defied death,
and they've also defeated Twelve Kizukis.
A good attitude to have!
That is why Hashiras receive
respect and preferential treatment.
So, Tanjiro, mind your manners
when you speak.
Y-Yes, sir!
One more thing. Sanemi...
Obanai...
Don't torment the younger ones too much.
As you wish.
Tanjiro, we have concluded
our business with you.
You may step back.
In that case, allow me
to take Kamado into my house.
All right, then!
Take them away please!
Pardon me for cutting in front of you!
KAKUSHI
Now then, let us begin the Hashira Meet—
Hold on a second!
Come back here!
Please allow me to head-butt
that man covered in scars!
I gotta—
Shut up! Keep your mouth shut!
I gotta head-butt him as many times
as he stabbed Nezuko!
Head-butting isn't a violation
of the Corps rules, right?
Shut up! Settle down now!
- Let go of me!
- Cut it out!
You're not allowed to interrupt the Master.
- We beg your pardon!
- We beg your pardon, Master!
- Master Tokito!
- We beg your pardon!
We beg your pardon!
We assure you that this boy
will be severely reprimanded, so—
Muichiro!
What a fine boy!
So please! Please!
So cool!
Just get out of our sight.
- Yes, sir!
Tanjiro...
Give Miss Tamayo my regards.
Hold up a second!
I just heard him
mention Miss Tamayo's name!
Don't you say another word!
- We got yelled at because of you!
- I thought I'd pee my pants!
You don't know
how terrifying the Hashiras are!
Try to read the room! Read it!
- I'll never forgive you as long as I live!
- I'll never forgive you!
- Apologize!
- Apologize! Apologize!
I...
I'm sorry.
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
Hello! Is anyone home?
Hello...
Jeez, no one's coming to the door.
Let's go check out the yard.
Hey, walk on your own.
I'm sorry.
It's just that my whole body
is aching like crazy.
The headquarters was huge, too,
but this mansion's something else, huh?
Come to think of it, was this place
called the "Butterfly Mansion"?
Hey, there's someone.
Someone's here.
That would be, um...
Oh, right! The Tsuguko...
Her name is...
Tsuguko?
It's Master Kanao Tsuyuri.
It's the girl from Final Selection.
Hey, somebody's forgotten how they got
stomped on by Master Kanao last night.
A Tsuguko is a swordsman
trained by a Hashira.
Only the ones with mind-blowing
skills and talent get chosen.
She's a girl, but she's awesome!
Please forgive us, Master Tsuyuri.
We were ordered to come here
by Master Kocho.
Permission to enter the mansion?
Uh, do you mind?
You don't mind, do you?
And who are you?
- Uh...
- We were ordered by Master Kocho!
Are you a Kakushi?
You've brought an injured person, right?
Please come this way.
Uh, right!
She's fast!
Five times?
I gotta take this five times? A day?
And I have to keep taking
this medicine for three months?
If I take this, I can't eat
anything, you know!
I mean it's really bitter!
It's such an ordeal!
So, you mean my arms and legs will heal
just by taking medicine? For real?
Listen, are they really gonna heal?
Tell me how they're gonna get healed!
Please stop shouting, will you?
Somebody explain this to me better!
So, that guy is still making
a commotion.
What's gonna happen if I forget
to take it even once? Hey!
Listen! My arms and legs!
What's gonna happen to my arms and legs? Hey!
What's gonna happen if I forget
to take it? Hey! Hey! Hey!
Zenitsu!
MEDICINE
For Zenitsu Agatsuma
Take 5 times daily
7 days' worth
After each meal
Please try to be quiet!
Didn't we already explain it
to you numerous times?
If you don't stop this nonsense now,
we'll tie you up!
Really now!
Zenitsu!
Are you okay? Did you hurt yourself?
So you did come up the mountain after all!
T-Tanjiro...
Tanjiro! Listen to me, will you?
I got stung by this stinky spider,
and the poison hurt like crazy, okay?
And that girl's been yelling at me
all this time! I hate my life!
Hey, get away from me.
I've got nothing to do with this.
Zenitsu, did you get smaller or something?
I almost got turned into a spider.
My arms and legs
are really short right now.
Is that right?
Where's Inosuke?
Have you seen Murata?
I don't know about anyone named Murata,
but Inosuke's right next to me.
Hey, you're right!
He's been here all this time!
And I didn't notice!
Inosuke, I'm so glad you're all right!
I'm so glad you're all right!
I'm so sorry! I couldn't rescue you!
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Paper! Paper!
Do something about this!
Your voice...
Is that you, Inosuke?
Wipe it! Hey! Do you hear me? Hey!
I heard he lost his voice or something.
I don't have all the details,
but I heard he, like, got hit in the neck,
and when he yelled at the top of his lungs
at the end, that finished it off.
And it did a number on his throat.
He's depressed now, so it's made him
gentle, and it really cracks me up!
Why are you cackling
in that creepy way all of a sudden?
What's going on?
I'm sorry for being so weak.
Hang in there, Inosuke!
It's not like you to get depressed!
Come on, you did good!
You're awesome!
I'm just so happy that you're alive!
Did I take my morning meds?
Did you see me take them?
Somebody? Did you see?
Zenitsu...
Inosuke...
Thank goodness.
You're alive.
It's all right now.
They said you could use
this room, Nezuko.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I really got roughed up
on Mt. Natagumo.
It hurts a lot.
To be honest, it hurts like crazy.
Nezuko...
Thanks for protecting me
on the mountain.
Who would've guessed that not only you,
but Mr. Urokodaki
and Mr. Tomioka, as well...
They're all risking their lives for us.
They're all taking care of us.
I need to...
become stronger.
Even today...
The Master more or less
saved both your life and mine.
That man's voice...
It was so soothing in a mysterious way.
Just listening to him speak
made my head feel light.
I wonder what kind of person he is.
Oh, right.
You're sleep-deprived, aren't you?
I'm hurting, and this is tough,
but I gotta keep on fighting.
Because...
I'll be a grown man one day.
And then,
I'll become an old guy and die.
the demon Nezuko will end up all alone.
That would be too lonely,
wouldn't it, Nezuko?
I promise you I'll turn you
back into a human, okay?
Just as you've all reported,
the demons' carnage
has increased more than ever.
Meaning that the threat to human life
is greater than it's ever been.
We'll have to bolster the ranks
of the Demon Slayers.
What do you all think?
The incident on Mt. Natagumo
made it crystal clear.
The caliber of Demon Slayers
has nose-dived to unbelievable levels.
Most of them are useless.
The trainers must be blind.
You'd think they could at least tell
if someone's competent or not.
Well, that kid today
sure seemed competent.
He did land that flamboyant blow on you,
Shinazugawa. He's got potential.
The more the human population increases,
the harder it becomes
to control and unify them.
Not to mention that the times
have changed considerably in this era.
Other than those who've had their loved ones
brutally massacred, and joined the Corps,
or those of distinguished pedigree
who have hunted demons for generations,
to ask anyone to harness as much
or even greater resolve and drive
to produce results would be cruel.
Still, considering that boy ran into a Twelve Kizuki
so soon after joining the Corps...
He may have the power to draw them!
Even we rarely get the chance
to confront one! It makes me envious!
Agreed.
But the fact that Lower Five
made such a drastic move
probably means that Muzan
is nowhere near Mt. Natagumo.
After all, as in the case of Asakusa,
whenever Muzan wishes
to hide something,
he creates a clever diversion
to throw us off.
It's really quite frustrating.
But those demons are still freely devouring
humans, gaining strength and surviving.
For the sake of those who have died,
there is only one thing for us to do.
I believe that among you Hashiras
who are present today,
I've assembled the finest unit since
the First Breathing swordsmen of the feudal era.
Tengen Uzui.
Kyojuro Rengoku.
Shinobu Kocho.
Mitsuri Kanroji.
Muichiro Tokito.
Gyomei Himejima.
Sanemi Shinazugawa.
Obanai Iguro.
Giyu Tomioka.
My children,
I look forward to your success.
Muzan Kibutsuji,
I swear I'll defeat you
if it's the last thing that I do.
We will bring you down without fail.
PREVIEW
I still find it hard to believe
that some demons don't attack humans.
It must be a miracle or something.
If you're gonna go there, then,
us trying to find a clue about Kibutsuji is...
well, what you call a "millennial miracle"!
That's a typical and flamboyant
idea if I ever heard one!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I hear that the Master is the 97th leader
of the Demon Slayer Corps!
To make sure we don't squander
this opportunity,
we Hashiras need to be the glue that holds
the Demon Slayer Corps together!
Are you mentally prepared
for that, Sound Hashira?
You don't have to remind me,
Fire Hashira!
Next, Episode 24,
"Rehabilitation Training"!
TO BE CONTINUED
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6y23s
Help other users to choose the best subtitles