( Wind blowing )
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
( Tanjiro inhales )
( Grunts )
( Gasps )
( Sabito sighs )
( Singing in Japanese )
( Women vocalizing )
Tanjiro: There's a reason I won,
because I learned how
to detect the opening thread.
As soon as I pick up the scent,
I'm able to see the thread.
It guides me.
( Thread rings )
It connects my blade to
any opening the enemy leaves me,
and it tightens
as soon as I see it.
It quickly draws
my blade forward.
Then I strike.
¶
( wind blowing )
( Footsteps crunching )
Urokodaki.
Urokodaki: To be honest,
I never had any intention
of sending you
to the final selection.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Urokodaki: Because I didn't want
to see any more children die.
I was sure you wouldn't be able
to cut through
this Boulder, but...
Well done, Tanjiro.
Truly remarkable.
I'm very proud.
( Tanjiro gasping )
¶
Urokodaki:
Make sure you come back
from final selection alive.
Your sister and I
will be waiting for you.
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Tanjiro gasps )
There's so much food.
What's the deal?
Urokodaki:
You finished your training,
so we're celebrating.
Time to eat. Don't be shy.
( Tanjiro chuckles )
Thank you. I'm starving.
Urokodaki: Tanjiro...
I'm afraid there's nothing more
I can do for you.
After today, you will be facing
unimaginable hardships.
Your training
pales in comparison.
But, at least for tonight,
you can rest well
and sleep soundly one last time.
( Shears snipping )
( Snipping continues )
Hey, Tanjiro.
Tanjiro: Eh? Yes?
Urokodaki: What did
you think of the hot pot?
Tanjiro: Great! I haven't
feasted like that in a while.
Urokodaki: A growing boy
with an appetite like yours
will get bigger and stronger,
the bigger his meals are.
The same applies to demons.
Remember that.
The more humans
a Demon has eaten,
the more powerful he'll be.
Tanjiro: So, if they eat a lot,
they'll be tough to defeat?
Urokodaki: That's right.
They get stronger,
physical traits change,
and some learn
to use strange spells.
You'll be able to tell
how many poor souls
they've claimed
once your sense of smell
is even more developed.
Tanjiro: What's this?
It is called a warding mask.
It's been enchanted
by a protection spell
to keep you from harm.
Tanjiro: Now it makes sense.
( Birds chirping )
Tanjiro: Nezuko.
I promise.
I'm going to come back for you.
Urokodaki: No need
to worry about your sister.
I'll take good care
of her for you.
Tanjiro: Thanks for everything.
Guess I'm off. See you later!
Say hi to Sabito and Makomo!
Urokodaki: Eh?
Tanjiro? That's impossible.
How does he know
the names of the dead?
( Women vocalizing )
Tanjiro: Wisteria.
It's all over the place.
I thought
it was out of season.
( Gasps )
¶
So many people.
- Guides: Good evening.
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Guides: Tonight
you've come to enter
the Demon Slayer Corps's
final selection.
Thank you all for being here.
Guide: Here on mount fujikasane,
there are several demons
that were captured alive
by Demon Slayer swordsmen.
They are kept here
for this event.
Guide 2: The Wisteria blossoms
prevent them from leaving.
They bloom
on this mountain year-round,
and they cover everything from
the base to halfway to the top.
Guide 1:
But the Wisteria ends here,
so demons abound
from this point on,
and they're very hungry.
Guide 2: In order
to complete final selection,
you must survive for seven days
beyond the Wisteria's
protection.
Guides: Now your trial begins.
( Tanjiro grunts )
( Whistling )
( Tanjiro panting )
Survive.
Don't think about anything else.
I just have to make it
through the night.
Once the sun comes up,
the demons
won't be able to do anything.
That'll be my chance to rest.
Which means
I need to head east,
make my way to where
the sunlight will hit first.
( Gasps )
I smell a Demon close by.
( Women vocalizing )
( Soft rustling )
Where is it?
Where's it coming from?
I can't seem to pin it down.
( Gasps ) Up there!
( Demon screeches )
( Women vocalizing )
( Demon laughs )
Tanjiro: Found you.
( Demon 2 growls )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Demon 1: Damn you!
Why don't you
go find your own snack?
This is my turf!
Demon 2: Your turf?
Ah, go to hell!
- ( Heart beating )
- Tanjiro: Two already.
- Can I handle them?
- Demon 2: Says who?
Demon 1: I saw him first!
Demon 2: Doesn't matter!
I'll be the first to kill him!
( Tanjiro gasps )
( Demons yell )
Tanjiro: You've got this.
Calm down, and watch closely.
Don't forget your training.
Demon 2: Haven't tasted
human flesh in forever!
Tanjiro: Total concentration.
Water breathing!
( Inhales )
I smell the thread.
( Thread rings )
Fourth form!
Striking tide!
( Demons groan )
( Tanjiro panting )
I did it.
( Flesh crackling )
I killed demons.
I'm getting stronger!
So my training
wasn't for nothing.
I did master it.
Nothing's left behind
when a Demon's killed
with this sword,
not even the bones.
( Birds chirping )
Urokodaki: A Demon's
weakest at the neck.
However, a normal sword
is useless, even upon the neck.
Tanjiro: Okay.
So how do I kill them?
Tanjiro:
With a Demon Slayer's katana
forged by
a special type of steel.
That's the only weapon
that can kill a Demon.
It's called a nichirin sword.
( Flesh crackling )
Tanjiro: Rest in peace.
( Sniffs )
( Gags ) What the--
what's that awful smell?
( Boy screams )
What the hell?!
I didn't sign up for this!
Tanjiro: What?
( Gasps )
( Rustling )
My god. What is that?
Makomo: Hey, Sabito.
You think Tanjiro can beat him?
Sabito: I don't know.
It seems nothing's
ever going to be enough.
You saw for yourself,
didn't you?
( Boy panting )
What's this mutated Demon
doing here?
Nobody said anything!
( Demon growling )
( Women vocalizing )
( Tanjiro shudders )
( Demon groans )
( Boy gasping )
Tanjiro: Swallowed whole!
( Demon gobbling )
( Growling )
( Boy gasping )
No!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Screams )
( Tanjiro gasps )
Stay strong!
Save him. Save him. Save him.
You're not powerless anymore!
Move it!
Water breathing, second form!
Water wheel!
( Boy grunts )
( Demon grunts )
Well, look at that.
It's another one
of those sweet little foxes.
Tanjiro: "Another"?
Say, fox cub, the year?
Are we still in meiji?
( Tanjiro gasps )
It's the taisho period!
Demon: Taisho?
( Screams )
Already?!
We have passed
into a new period?!
Again!
And I'm still stuck
inside this Wisteria prison!
( Screams )
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Damn you, Urokodaki!
Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
Tanjiro: You know Urokodaki?
Demon: Of course I do.
Urokodaki's the one
who captured me
and brought me here!
But that was 47 years ago now,
back when he was
still hunting demons like me,
the edo period,
during the keio era.
Tanjiro: No way. Edo period?
Boy: You lie!
No Demon could ever live
that long in here!
Besides, all these demons have
only eaten two or three humans!
They die during final selection.
In fact, they even
eat their own kind!
Demon: And yet I've managed
to survive here all this time,
trapped in this flowery cage.
I've managed to devour
at least 50 of you brats.
Tanjiro: 50 people?!
Demon: 11...
12...
13.
That means you're number 14.
Tanjiro: What are
you talking about?
( Demon giggles )
That's how many of Urokodaki's
students I've eaten.
( Laughs )
I promised myself i'd
kill every single one of them.
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
- Demon: You know,
the ones who stood out to me
the most were those two.
Ah, yes.
The boy's hair
was an unusual shade of pink,
a scar by his mouth.
He was the most powerful
of the lot.
The other one was a girl
who wore a flowery kimono,
small, not much power,
but awfully agile.
( Tanjiro gasps )
So they were dead?
Killed by this Demon?
But I was with them.
Demon: Your mask,
that's what gives you away
as one of Urokodaki's brats.
Easy to spot the texture
of one of the masks he's carved.
They always match the style
of the tengu mask he wears.
He calls them "warding masks,"
right?
Except that's
how I pick out who to eat.
They're all inside my belly.
It's as if he's guided them
to their deaths.
( Giggles )
When I told the girl,
she started crying
and fell into a rage.
( Laughs )
But it wasn't long
before she lost
all control of her movement.
( Laughs )
I ripped her limb from limb
and feasted!
( Tanjiro growls )
( Demon growls )
( Tanjiro yells )
Sabito: Calm down, Tanjiro.
Your breathing is uneven.
Stay focused. Forget about US.
( Boy gasping )
You're on your own, buddy.
I'm getting out of here.
( Women vocalizing )
( Demon laughing )
There goes another one
of Urokodaki's brats.
( Giggles )
I wonder, how will he feel
when another one of his children
doesn't make it back home?
Oh, I wish I could see
the look on his face.
( Laughs )
I bet it's
going to be priceless.
If only I could be there.
( Shigeru faintly ) Tanjiro!
Tanjiro!
( Tanjiro gasps )
Demon: What's this?
He can still move.
That means I can have some fun!
¶
Tanjiro: Damn!
I can't just cut his arms off.
They regrow too fast!
Demon: That's not
going to be enough
for you to beat me,
little fox.
But, then again,
not even that pink-haired brat
could cut off my head!
( Tanjiro growls )
There's no way
I can just let him go.
I won't let another life
be sacrificed.
No more! I'll take him down!
( Yelling )
( Sniffs )
Wait a second. Underground!
Demon: H-he jumped!
Damn it, how did he know?
No matter.
He won't be able
to dodge an attack in midair!
Makomo: Do you think
he's going to beat Tanjiro, too?
His neck is thick.
Can it be cut?
Sabito: I can't say
whether he'll win or lose today.
However, one fact
is irrefutable either way.
Tanjiro cut
through this Boulder,
the toughest
and largest Boulder of them all.
Demon: He deflected it!
( Tanjiro yells )
Total concentration.
- ( Inhales )
- Water breathing!
¶
Demon: I let him get too close.
Not to worry. My neck is tough.
He can't cut through it.
Tanjiro: First form!
Demon: As soon as he fails,
I'm going to grab his head
and crush it,
just like I did
to the other one!
( Thread rings )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Tanjiro yells )
( Demon grunts )
Tanjiro: Water surface slash!
( Singing in Japanese )
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org