Demon: Your mask is
what gives you away.
( Laughs ) Except that's
how I pick out who to eat.
( Tanjiro growls )
( Demon growls )
( Tanjiro yells )
¶
Total concentration.
- ( Inhales )
- Water breathing!
( Chorus vocalizing )
First form!
( Thread rings )
( Tanjiro yells )
Water surface slash!
( Singing in Japanese )
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-
( Women vocalizing )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Blood spurts )
¶
( Demon panting )
( Panting continues )
Demon: Urokodaki!
No! No! No!
My body's falling apart
and disappearing,
and I can't stop it!
Damn it.
The face of this Demon Slayer
is the last thing
I'm ever going to see.
I never would have thought
it'd come to this.
( Boy crying )
I'm so scared.
I'm all alone now.
( Crying )
Brother, where are you?
I want you to hold my hand again
like you always do.
( Boy's voice )
Why? Why did I do it?
Why would I eat
my own big brother?
Huh?
I had a brother?
I'd forgotten.
( Flesh crackling )
Tanjiro: What a sad scent.
¶
please, god, help him.
The next time
this man is reborn,
please don't let him
turn into a Demon again.
( Boy panting )
- Brother!
- Brother: Hmm?
Boy: Brother, wait up!
Can you please hold my hand?
Brother: You scaredy-cat.
You're hopeless.
You know that?
¶
Tanjiro: Sabito, Makomo...
And all the others whose lives
were taken by this Demon...
It's over.
You can rest now.
Finally you're
going home as promised,
back to mount sagiri,
if only as souls.
You're going back to Urokodaki.
If I had failed, that's where
my soul would have gone, too.
( Demon panting )
¶
( Growling )
Tanjiro: I've got a question!
Once someone's
been turned into a Demon,
how do they change back?
( Branches creak )
( Thunder rumbles )
( Running footsteps )
( Demons growl )
Tanjiro: Someone, please,
tell me.
How do I turn Nezuko back?!
( Panting )
( Sniffs )
( Grunts )
( Bird warbling )
That's Wisteria.
( Sighs )
I made it.
¶
( birds chirping )
Only four of US?
We started with over 20.
So he didn't make it.
( No audible dialogue )
He's gone,
and it's all
because I blacked out.
I couldn't save him.
Boy: I'm gonna die.
I'm done for.
I've survived for now,
but, soon enough, dead.
Guides: Welcome back, everyone.
Guide: And congratulations.
Guide 2: We're pleased
to see you're safe.
Boy 2: So? I made it back alive.
What do I do now?
Where's my sword?
Guide 1: Patience. We must
first issue you all uniforms.
We'll start by taking
your measurements.
Next, your rank will be engraved
on the back of your hand.
Guide 2: For your reference,
there are ten ranks in total.
Guide 1: Kinoe.
Guide 2: Kinoto.
Guide 1: Hinoe.
Guide 2: Hinoto.
Guide 1: Tsuchinoe.
Guide 2: Tsuchinoto.
Guide 1: Kanoe.
Guide 2: Kanoto.
Guide 1: Mizunoe.
Guide 2: Mizunoto.
Guide 1: You all
start at mizunoto.
This is the lowest rank
in the Demon Slayer Corps.
Boy 2: And our swords?
Guide 1: In a moment,
you will be given the chance
to select the ore that will be
used to forge your swords.
However,
it will be 10 to 15 days
before the weapons
are ready for you.
( Boy 2 groans ) Really?
Guide 1: But first...
- ( Birds squawking )
- Tanjiro: Eh?
( Boys gasping )
Guide 2: Now that
you're Demon slayers,
you must each be assigned
your own Kasugai Crow.
Tanjiro: We get crows, then?
What for?
Guide 1: The kasugai crows
are primarily used
to facilitate communication.
Boy 1: Wait. "Crows"?
Isn't this a sparrow?
Sparrow: I don't need this crap!
- ( Crow squawking )
- ( Boy 2 growls )
Who the hell cares
about some stupid crow?!
Tanjiro: Eh?
( Boys gasp )
Boy 2: I want
my sword right now.
Give it to me
before I get angry,
the color changing katana.
I want it now! Do you hear me?!
Huh?
Tanjiro: Take your hand off her,
or I'll break your arm. Now!
- ( Boy 1 stammering )
- Boy 2: Huh?
Who the hell are you?
( Boy 1 wails )
Wh-what do I do?!
Boy 2: Give it your best shot.
( Tanjiro inhales )
( Arm creaks )
( Boy 2 screams )
( Boy 1 gasps )
( Boy 2 gasping )
( Groans )
Guide 2: Are you finished
chatting with each other?
( Boy 2 growls ) Eh?
¶
guide 2: Now the time has come.
Please select an ore
to use for your sword.
The steel you will use
to protect yourself and
to annihilate countless demons
will be that
of your own choosing.
Boy 1: I'm gonna be dead
soon anyway, probably.
Tanjiro: They want US to choose,
but how are we
supposed to pick one?
I've never even
laid eyes on ore.
I can't tell the difference
between any of them.
Boy 2: I don't have
a clue what to pick.
Tanjiro: Mm?
( Gasps )
( Sniffs )
Boy 2: Huh?
Man: Really?
Five of them
managed to survive?
That's excellent.
The number of my children
continues to grow.
What kinds of swordsmen
will they be?
)
( Tanjiro panting )
I'm so naive...
And a fool.
I couldn't even
get a Demon to talk to me.
All any of them
wanted to do was kill me.
Ah, Nezuko. I'm sorry.
I'm no closer to finding a cure,
to making her human again.
- ( Bell rings )
- ( No audible laughter )
( Groans )
My uniform feels heavy.
I wanna get home...
But every part of me hurts.
( Grunting )
( Panting )
I made it.
Nezuko.
Urokodaki.
( Gasps )
Nezuko!
It's you! You're awake!
( Groans )
( Wails )
Why'd you do that?
Why'd you have to sleep
for so long?
I thought you were
never gonna wake up!
I was afraid
you were gonna die!
Urokodaki: You're here.
You came back alive.
( Tanjiro weeping )
( Birds warbling )
¶
Urokodaki: You did it.
You were able to kill
that mutated Demon.
Tanjiro: Yes.
Urokodaki: Then, it's over.
I'm truly impressed
that you made it back.
Tanjiro: Thanks.
Urokodaki: You should know
there are
different kinds of demons.
The blood Demon art
is a special spell
that some use
to give them abilities.
- Tanjiro: Eh?
- Urokodaki: You may end up
having to face some of them
in the near future as well,
and fighting
against supernatural abilities
will be more difficult
than anything you've done.
Still, Tanjiro, I have no doubt
that you'll be just fine.
( Tanjiro gasps )
Right.
So it seems like Nezuko's
a whole lot different
from other demons.
Do you think that's because of
this bloody art thingie, then?
Urokodaki: No, I think
it's something else.
I wouldn't call that an example
of the blood Demon art.
This is only a guess,
but I believe Nezuko can recover
her strength by sleeping,
instead of consuming human flesh
as other demons do.
Tanjiro: Don't worry.
I'll protect you, Nezuko.
( Bells tinkling )
Mm?
¶
Hi there.
Haganezuka:
My name is Haganezuka.
I've forged
Tanjiro Kamado's sword.
I am here to deliver it.
Tanjiro: Oh!
Sorry. I'm Tanjiro Kamado.
Come in.
Haganezuka:
This is a nichirin sword.
I forged it myself.
Tanjiro: Um...
Do you wanna come in,
have some--
Haganezuka: The materials
for this kind of sword
only come from the mountain
closest to the sun,
made of Scarlet iron sand
and Scarlet ore, unique.
They produce steel
that can absorb sunlight.
Tanjiro: Wow, really?
Haganezuka: You see, mount yoko
is bathed in sunlight all day,
never a cloud in the...
Urokodaki: The man still refuses
to listen to a word
anyone else says.
- Haganezuka: Eh?
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
- A clown mask?
- Haganezuka: Hmm? Hmm?!
Hey, you're a child
of brightness, aren't you?
( Chuckles )
Well, isn't that lucky?
Tanjiro: Uh, my parents's names
were tanjuro and kie.
Haganezuka:
That's not what I mean.
You know how your hair and eyes
have a reddish hue to them?
When a family that works
with fire has a child like you,
it's considered lucky
and cause for celebration.
Tanjiro: Is it, really?
I had no idea.
Haganezuka: That means
there's a good chance
this sword will turn red.
Right, Urokodaki?
Urokodaki: Yes.
Haganezuka: Come on.
Draw it, already.
Nichirin swords
are also referred to
as "color changing katanas,"
because,
depending on the bearer,
they change color.
Tanjiro: Eh?
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
Haganezuka: Black?!
Urokodaki: That's interesting.
Tanjiro: Why? Does turning black
mean something bad?
- ( Haganezuka shuddering )
- Tanjiro: Is it unlucky?
Urokodaki: No, no. It's just
that it's a little unusual.
You don't see it often.
It's pitch-black.
( Haganezuka gags )
But I was really hoping
I'd get to see
a sword turn bright red!
Damn it!
- ( Shrieks )
- ( Tanjiro gasps )
Ouch! Hey, let go!
Stop! Please! Ow!
How old are you, anyway?
Haganezuka: I'm 37!
( Crow squawking )
¶
Tanjiro: Huh?
Crow: Tanjiro Kamado,
I bring you orders.
Tanjiro: Huh? It can talk?
Crow: You must go to a town
northwest of here,
and hurry.
Young girls are disappearing.
( Tanjiro gasps )
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
( No audible dialogue )
Crow: Night after night,
at least one of them vanishes!
You must hunt down the Demon
responsible and destroy it!
Tanjiro Kamado,
prepare yourself well!
This is your first assignment
as a member
of the Demon Slayer Corps!
Tanjiro: All right.
It's time.
( Singing in Japanese )
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/77ckm
Help other users to choose the best subtitles