Fearsome monsters... Exotic creatures...
Vast riches... Hidden treasures...
Evil enclaves... Unexplored lands...
The word "unknown" holds magic.
And some incredible people are
drawn to that magic.
They are known...
...as Hunters!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I see, I see...
That settles it...
You're the real one.
Examiners are Hunters
selected by the committee to perform
this duty without pay.
Any Hunter, bearing the title we seek,
would have been able to block that attack.
I shall take that as a compliment.
However, should you attack me again,
for any reason,
I will report you for turning
on an examiner.
And you will be immediately disqualified.
Are we clear?
Sure.
Hisoka x Is x Sneaky
The 368 applicants who made it through
the long underground tunnel
find themselves in an unexplored land
teeming with strange creatures,
known as the Numere Wetlands.
Pay attention now.
Be sure to stay close behind me.
The fog is getting thicker.
All right...
This is our chance.
We'll take advantage of the fog
to get rid of him!
Gon...
Huh?
Let's move up.
Okay.
We don't want to lose sight
of the examiner.
I'm more concerned with
increasing the distance between
us and Hisoka.
Staying too close to him is dangerous.
I can smell it in the air.
Smell?
Hmm...
I don't think he smells.
Leorio! Kurapika!
Killua says that we should move up!
Hey...
Can't you feel the tension
surrounding us?
Moron!
If I had the strength,
I'd already be there!
Don't worry about us!
What?
Let's go, Gon.
Ah, wait!
We can't even tell
which way we're going.
It's okay.
As long as we don't lose sight
of the guys ahead of us...
What's going on?
Wh-What?
Noggin Luggin' Tortoise
This looks bad...
Claymore Mushrooms
Huh? What?
A butterfly?
Hypnosis Butterfly
Damn!
Which way are we supposed to go?
Did we lose sight of him?
Pay attention now.
Be sure to stay close behind me.
Over there!
Pay attention now.
Caw!
Be sure to stay close behind me.
Ruse Raven
Caw!
That thing can imitate human speech?
Close call...
Yeah...
I hear people screaming all around us.
Just stay on your guard.
I wonder if Leorio and
Kurapika are okay...
Mm?
Frog-in-Waiting
Leorio!
Ouch.
Leorio, here's our opportunity.
Y-Yeah...
Guess he didn't like the taste of us.
It was this.
That was from Tonpa-san!
Guess he saved us.
Well, I could have escaped.
I'm still worried about Leorio and Kurapika.
Forget about them. Let's get a move on.
We can still catch up to the examiner.
We've lost sight of the front-runners.
Which way should we go?
Stop!
Over there...
When I saw you last year,
I knew you weren't Hunter material.
We'll spare you if you swear not to
take the Hunter Exam again.
Sure.
Huh?
I'm passing the exam this year,
so I won't need to retake it.
Passing?
Idiot!
Look at this fog.
It's impossible to determine which
direction the main pack went!
Meaning we've all failed the exam!
So that's why.
Having already failed, you wish
to play examiner.
Hunters require prey.
Why don't I play examiner...
And judge whether you
are Hunter material?
Shut up!
Now, then...
H-H-Help!
Hel—
Well?
Care to participate,
in my little game of examiner?
Hunter Vocabulary
Satotz
Cool...
We've caught up to the
main group, Gon.
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Leorio.
On my signal, we run in
opposite directions.
What?
He is vastly more experienced
in real combat.
The two of us won't stand a
chance against him.
We cannot afford to squander time
in a pointless fight!
Now!
I see...
A wise decision.
Hmm?
I just can't do it...
This may not be my fight,
but I won't close my eyes
and make a break for it!
Leorio?!
Mm, I adore that look on your face.
What?
Gon?
I made it in time...
Not bad, little boy.
Is that a fishing pole?
What a fascinating weapon.
Allow me a closer look.
Your fight is with
me!
You came to rescue your friend?
Such a good boy.
And that expression...
Nice...
Very nice.
I'm getting excited now...
Okay!
How wonderful...
I really do love that look.
Do not fear.
I will not kill your friend.
He passed.
Yes, you pass, as well.
Grow up and become a fine Hunter.
Hisoka, you should get back here.
We're nearly at the Phase Two site.
Okay, I'll be right there.
It's always good to have friends.
You can find your own way back, yes?
That's a good boy.
Gon!
Are you all right?
Huh?
Gon isn't here...
This way.
You can really tell?
Uh-huh.
Leorio's cologne is very unique.
I can smell him from a
few kilometers away.
Say, Kurapika...
What did Hisoka mean when
he said that we passed?
Hisoka was acting as a judge.
A judge?
Yes.
He must have his own benchmarks
for evaluating power.
It's possible that he was ascertaining
each applicant's strength.
Apparently, you and Leorio must
have met his standards.
I see.
But I was powerless to do
anything against him.
Didn't you land your first hit on him?
Only because I surprised him.
Besides, Leorio passed,
even though he lost...
Hmm...
Perhaps he sensed that you
were kindred spirits.
Kindred spirits?
I seriously doubt that Hisoka
could qualify as a Hunter.
However,
I must admit that he did impress me
with his superhuman agility
and graceful technique.
It's quite common that those
possessing special talents are drawn
to others with unique gifts.
Most likely, Hisoka's instincts
and experience
told him that you had the skill and
potential to become Hunters.
Killing you now would have been a waste...
That was his perspective.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Was that insensitive on my part?
No...
But I was pretty excited, as well.
I was so scared, I wanted to run away.
But I couldn't.
And at the same time, I was excited.
Isn't that strange?
For the first time in his life,
Gon has experienced mortal fear.
Though the unfamiliar feelings
accompanying that fear confuse Gon,
he cannot restrain his growing curiosity.
At this stage, 220 candidates have
withdrawn from the exam,
leaving 148 remaining applicants.
Next time: A x Surprising x Challenge!
S-Surprisingly challenging.
Huh?
Gon, are you okay?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6xv3a
Help other users to choose the best subtitles